retrevo.com 2013-04-03

# Privacy Policy | Retrevo

Retrevo takes the privacy and security of your Personal Information very seriously. Retrevo does not share, disclose or sell your personally identifiable information collected online with other companies or organizations. Keeping your trust is vital to the success of our business. We want you to know that we apply our long standing commitment to safeguarding the privacy of all of our users, their Personal Information and activities on Retrevos web site. If you want to read the long version, you can continue to the long version of our Privacy Policy below. 

This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use, disclosure, security and integrity of any Personal Information you submit to us using our web site or otherwise. Personal Information is information that personally identifies you such as your name, mailing address, email address or phone number. 

Collection of Personal Information

We require you to register with us to use certain parts of our service. During registration and subsequent use of our service, we may collect the following types of information: 

  * Information you provide: When you register for the Retrevo service, we ask you for Personal Information such as your name and email address, demographic information such as gender and zip code, and product usage information. We also collect information you volunteer to us on surveys and feedback forms. When you send us an email, we use your email address so we can respond to your query. If you apply for a job at Retrevo, we will collect any information contained in the email message you send to us as well as information contained in your resume.
  * Cookies: Retrevo may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small data file sent to your browser from a web server to be stored on your hard drive that allows easier access the next time the same page is visited. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Retrevo features and services may not function properly if you disable cookies in your browser.
  * Preference Based Advertising: We also work with and permit certain third parties, including advertising networks and website analysis firms, to place cookies on your computer/browser when you visit our Sites. These third party cookies are used to gather non-PII about your activities on our Sites and third party sites to serve you with advertisements while you are on third party sites (“Third-Party Ads”). If you do not wish to participate in this activity, please [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) to opt-out. 

Some important notes: (1) the opt-out tools for Third-Party Ads include all the advertising networks that Retrevo works with, but also many that Retrevo does not work with; (2) opting out of Our Ads does not automatically serve as an opt-out from Third-Party Ads – the same is true the other way around. To opt-out of Our Ads and Third-Party Ads, you must use each respective opt-out tool above; (3) the opt-out tools for both Our Ads and Third-Party Ads rely on cookies to ensure that your non-PII is not used for online advertising purposes (“Opt-out Cookies”). Therefore, if you buy a new computer, change web browsers or delete these Opt-out Cookies from your computer, you will need to perform the relevant opt-out tasks again; and (4) the features of your internet browser and/or certain add-on software may allow you to block or limit the use of cookies for preference based advertising and other purposes. We cannot, however, promise that our Sites will work well or be compatible with these alternative methods of blocking or limiting the use of cookies.

  * Log information: Your web browser sends some information automatically when you connect to a web server. This information may include the IP address of your computer, date and time of access, type of web browser used, the operating system and other information that uniquely identifies a browser. When you use the Retrevo service, our servers automatically record this information in log files. We also record search terms that you type, web pages you access and other information that may describe your behavior.
  * Links to other sites: Retrevo web site includes links to other external sites either directly or in response to a search query from you. Retrevo does not exercise control over these external sites. We advise you to review the individual privacy policies of the respective sites.

Use of Personal Information

In general, Retrevo uses Personal Information collected from you to respond to requests that you make, to provide you the stated service or to improve our service. Retrevo uses personal and usage information to: 

  * Process and satisfy the request, such as a job application, product support issue or complaint;
  * Maintain, protect and improve our service, including occasional communication with you regarding this;
  * Personalize the service including the content, display of relevant advertisements and additional services; Develop new products and services;
  * Introduce new products, services and offers to you, including communication with you regarding this.

Disclosure of Personal Information

Retrevo does not share, disclose or sell your personally identifiable information collected online with other companies or organizations. Personal Information is your name, email address, mailing address or phone number. We do share information with other companies or individuals outside of Retrevo in the following limited circumstances: 

  * We may share with our advertising and business partners certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as number of users [of a certain demographics or from a certain zip code] who searched for a certain term, or the number of users [of a certain demographics or from a certain zip code] who clicked on a certain advertisement, or number of users [of a certain demographics or from a certain zip code] who might be interested in a certain type of service based on analytics performed by Retrevo. This information will not be linked with any Personal Information.
  * We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on Retrevo; (b) protect and defend the rights, safety or property of Retrevo or users of our web site.
  * If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, the acquiring company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Your Choice Regarding Your Personal Information

You have the option of not providing us the Personal Information at the point where it is collected. It may result in unavailability of certain services to you. For example, we require user registration with a small number of mandatory fields. If you elect not to provide the requested information, you will not be able to register and use our service. 

You can review and validate the information that we have collected about you by sending an email to [privacy at retrevo dot com](mailto:privacy@retrevo.com) and requesting a review of your personal data. You have the option of (a) correcting this data if you believe it is inaccurate; or (b) delete this data. We make good faith efforts to correct this data or delete this data if is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. Deletion of certain data may result in unavailability of some services to you and you will be advised of such changes. 

You will occasionally receive emails from Retrevo requesting feedback about our current service, seeking desired improvements and/or announcing the availability of additional products and services. Retrevo does not rent or sell its email address lists. Spammers use well-known methods to hide their identity by using other people's email address to send out emails. If you have any question about the genuineness of an email you receive that appears to be from Retrevo, contact us at [privacy at retrevo dot com](mailto:privacy@retrevo.com). Do not furnish personal information in response to such an email. Retrevo does not request personal information in email messages. 

Data Security and Integrity

Retrevo processes Personal Information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We take commercially reasonable steps to make sure that our servers are protected against unauthorized access by using firewalls and physical security. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that only authorized personnel have access to your personal information and only for the purpose that it was collected. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the Personal Information we process is accurate, complete and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary by contacting us. No system can provide guaranteed security. We will notify you if at any point we become aware of a security breach. 

Retrevo Newsletters

We offer newsletters to our subscribers containing daily deals and the latest tech editorials. If you no longer wish to receive Retrevo Newsletters, you may opt-out by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the newsletters. 

Privacy Policy Updates

We will update our privacy policy from time to time to reflect changes in our business. If we make any substantial changes in the way we collect, use or disclose your Personal Information, we will post a notice on this page. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our web site. Continued use of our web site following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you via email that you supplied to us. You will be able to opt out of any new use of such Personal Information by contacting us. This Privacy Policy was last updated on September 9, 2011. 

Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us: 

Retrevo Inc. 

12200 W. Olympic Blvd. Ste 300

Los Angeles, CA 90064

email: privacy at retrevo dot com
